Guide to the James J. John papers, circa 1930-2016,
John, James J. papers,
- Series IV. General documents
  - Baron Franciscan: Poverty and Civic Wealth, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - "The Canons of Premontre" Documents, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1979-1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Catalogue Cards, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Catalogue Cards, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Catalogues and Notes, 1990-1997 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Ingolstadt Article, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - The College of Premontre Notes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - College Organization Notes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - The College of Premontre Notes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - The College of Premontre Notes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Chapters (College of Premontre), Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Paper on Canon Law, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - The College of Premontre Papers, Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Printed Matter, Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Postcards, Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Slides and Pictures, Undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - "In Search of Cult", Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1950-1992 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (German and Polish), Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Kehr um, Norbert! (German story), Undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Papers Concerning Prague, 1950-1973 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1977-1990 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Maps and Photos, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 29)